University Senate; Records ua200
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Legislation, 1966-2006; 3; 3.5 cubic ft.
  - 0708-27, 2007-2008 (Box 5 (3-Legislation), Folder 2)
  - 0708-28, 2007-2008 (Box 5 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 0708-29, 2007-2008 (Box 5 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 0708-30, 2007-2008 (Box 5 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 0708-31, 2007-2008 (Box 5 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 0708-32, 2007-2008 (Box 5 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 0708-33, 2007-2008 (Box 5 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 0708-34, 2007-2008 (Box 5 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 0708 Legislation - extra photocopies, 2007-2008 (Box 5 (3-Legislation), Folder 4)
- Meeting Records, 1964-2005; 4; 3.75 cubic ft.
  Arranged chronologically.
  Contains agendas, minutes and some discrete pieces of correspondence of the University Senate and its immediate predecessor, the Faculty Senate. At the end of the series are a number of audiotapes, arranged chronologically, of meeting proceedings and other matters. These tapes (1971-78, 1986-88) supplement the minutes.
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1964 December (Box 1 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 1)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1966 May-1967 May (Box 1 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 2)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1967 May-1968 May (Box 1 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 3)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1968 May-1968 December (Box 1 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 4)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1969 January-1969 May (Box 1 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 5)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1969 May-1969 October (Box 1 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 6)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1969 February-1970 December (Box 1 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 7)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1970 March-1970 April (Box 1 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 8)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1970 May-1970 November (Box 1 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 9)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1970 December-1971 March (Box 1 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 10)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1971 April-1971 May (Box 1 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 11)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1971 May-1971 December (Box 1 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 12)
  - Agendas and Minutes - Cassettes of Sirotkins of Report on the Budget (2 Cassettes), 1971 November 15 (Box 6 (4-Meeting Records), Cassette 1)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1971 December-1972 March (Box 1 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 13)
  - Attendance at Senate Meetings, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 14)
  - Agendas and Minutes - Cassettes of Governance Commission Report (3 Cassettes), 1972 January 24 (Box 6 (4-Meeting Records), Cassette 2)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1972 April-1972 May (Box 1 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 15)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1972 September-1972 November (Box 1 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 16)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1973 January-1973 March (Box 1 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 17)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1973 May-1973 November (Box 1 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 18)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1973 December -1974 April (Box 1 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 19)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1974 May-1975 January (Box 1 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 20)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1975 February-1975 December (Box 1 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 21)
  - Agendas and Minutes - Cassette of Budget Report (1 Cassette), 1975 December 01 (Box 6 (4-Meeting Records), Cassette 3)
  - Agendas and Minutes - Cassette of Budget Report (1 Cassette), 1976 January 26 (Box 6 (4-Meeting Records), Cassette 4)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1976 January-1976 October (Box 1 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 22)
  - Agendas and Minutes - Cassette of Mission Statement (1 Cassette), 1976 October 11 (Box 6 (4-Meeting Records), Cassette 5)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1976 November-1977 April (Box 1 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 23)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1977 September-1978 May (Box 2 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 1)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1978 May- 1978 November (Box 2 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 2)
  - Agendas and Minutes - Cassette of Meeting (1 Cassette), 1978 November 06 (Box 6 (4-Meeting Records), Cassette 6)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1978 December- 1979 October (Box 2 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 3)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1979 October-1980 December (Box 2 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 4)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1981 February-1981 December (Box 2 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 5)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1982 February-1982 December (Box 2 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 6)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1982 April- 1982 Deember (Box 2 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 7)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1983 February-1983 December (Box 2 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 8)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1984 March-1984 December (Box 2 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 9)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1985 February-1985 September (Box 2 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 10)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1985 November-1986 May (Box 2 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 11)
  - Agendas and Minutes - Audiotape (1 Cassette), 1986 October 06 (Box 6 (4-Meeting Records), Cassette 7)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1986 October-1987 October (Box 2 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 12)
  - Agendas and Minutes - Audiotape (1 Cassette), 1986 November 03 (Box 6 (4-Meeting Records), Cassette 9)
  - Agendas and Minutes - Audiotape (1 Cassette), 1987 February 09 (Box 6 (4-Meeting Records), Cassette 10)
  - Agendas and Minutes - Audiotape (2 Cassettes), 1987 May 04 (Box 6 (4-Meeting Records), Cassette 11)
  - Agendas and Minutes - Audiotape (1 Cassette), 1987 October 05 (Box 5 (4-Meeting Records), Cassette 1)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1987 November-1988 May (Box 2 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 13)
  - Agendas and Minutes - Audiotape (1 Cassette), 1987 December 07 (Box 5 (4-Meeting Records), Cassette 2)
  - Agendas and Minutes - Audiotape (1 Cassette), 1988 March 14 (Box 5 (4-Meeting Records), Cassette 3)
  - Agendas and Minutes - Audiotape (1 Cassette), 1988 April 18 (Box 5 (4-Meeting Records), Cassette 4)
  - Agendas and Minutes - Audiotape (2 Cassettes), 1988 May 02 (Box 5 (4-Meeting Records), Cassette 5)
  - Agendas and Minutes - Audiotape (2 Cassettes), 1988 May 04 (Box 5 (4-Meeting Records), Cassette 6)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1988 September-1989 April (Box 2 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 14)
  - Agendas and Minutes - Audiotape (1 Cassette), 1988 October 03 (Box 5 (4-Meeting Records), Cassette 7)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1989 May-1989 December (Box 2 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 15)
  - Secretary's Notebooks, 1989-1991 (Box 2 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 16)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1990 February-1990 May (Box 2 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 17)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1990 October-1991 April (Box 2 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 18)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1991 May-1992 February (Box 2 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 19)
  - Secretary's Notebooks, 1991-1992 (Box 2 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 20)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1992 March-1992 October (Box 3 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 1)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1992 November-1993 May (Box 3 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 2)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1993 October-1994 April (Box 3 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 3)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1994 May-1994 December (Box 3 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 4)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1995 February-1995 May (Box 3 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 5)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1995 October-1995 December (Box 3 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 6)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1996 February-1996 May (Box 3 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 7)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1996 Spetember-1996 December (Box 3 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 8)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1997 February-1997 May (Box 3 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 9)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1997 September-1998 March (Box 3 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 10)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1998 May (Box 3 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 11)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1998 September-1999 May (Box 3 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 12)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1999 May-1999 December (Box 3 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 13)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 2000 February-2000 May (Box 3 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 14)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 2000 May-2000 December (Box 3 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 15)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 2001 February-2001 May (Box 3 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 16)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 2001 October-2002 May (Box 3 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 17)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 2002 September-2002 December (Box 3 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 18)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 2003 February-2003 May (Box 3 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 19)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 2003 September-2003 November (Box 3 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 20)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 2003 December-2004 March (Box 3 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 21)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 2004 April-2004 May (Box 4 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 1)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 2004 October-2004 December (Box 4 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 2)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 2005 February-2005 May (Box 4 (4-Meeting Records), Folder 3)
  - Agendas and Minutes - Audiotapes (2 Cassettes), Undated (Box 6 (4-Meeting Records), Cassette 8)
- Formal Reports and Publications, 1946/1999; 5; 0.67 cubic ft.
  - Annual Report of the Faculty Council, 1946 (Box 1 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 1)
  - Annual Report of the Faculty Council, 1950-1951 (Box 1 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 2)
  - Annual Report of the Faculty Council, 1952-1953 (Box 1 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 3)
  - Annual Report of the Faculty Council, 1953-1954 (Box 1 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 4)
  - Annual Report of the Faculty Council, 1954-1955 (Box 1 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 5)
  - Annual Report of the Faculty Council, 1955-1956 (Box 1 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 6)
  - Annual Report of the Faculty Senate, 1956/1957 (Box 1 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 7)
  - Annual Report of the Faculty Council, 1957-1958 (Box 1 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 8)
  - Annual Report of the Faculty Council, 1958-1959 (Box 1 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 9)
  - Annual Report of the Faculty Council, 1959-1960 (Box 1 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 10)
  - Annual Report of the Faculty Council, 1960-1961 (Box 1 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 11)
  - Annual Report of the Faculty Council, 1961-1962 (Box 1 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 12)
  - Annual Report of the Faculty Council, 1962-1963 (Box 1 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 13)
  - Annual Report of the Faculty Council, 1963-1964 (Box 1 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 14)
  - Annual Report of the Faculty Council, 1965-1966 (Box 1 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 15)
  - Annual Reports of the Faculty Senate and Senate Councils, 1966-1967; 1969-1970 (Box 1 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 16)
  - Annual Report, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 17)
  - Annual Report, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 18)
  - Annual Report, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 19)
  - Annual Report, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 20)
  - Annual Report, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 21)
  - Annual Report, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 22)
  - Mission Statement of the University Department Responses (Folder 1 of 2), 1976 (Box 1 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 23)
  - Mission Statement of the University Department Responses (Folder 2 of 2), 1976 (Box 1 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 24)
  - Annual Report, 1976-1977 (Box 2 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 1)
  - Mission Statement of the University, 1976-1977 (Box 2 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 2)
  - Annual Report, 1977-1978 (Box 2 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 3)
  - Annual Report, 1978-1979 (Box 2 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 4)
  - Annual Report, 1979-1980; 1981-1982 (Box 2 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 5)
  - Annual Report, 1982-1983; 1985-1986 (Box 2 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 6)
  - Annual Report, 1987-1988; 1988-1989 (Box 2 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 7)
  - University Senate Newsletter, 1989 (Box 2 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 8)
  - Annual Report, 1989-1990 (Box 2 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 9)
  - Your Senate, 1991-1992 (Box 2 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 10)
  - Annual Report, 1991-1992; 1994-1995 (Box 2 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 11)
  - Annual Report, 1995-1996 (Box 2 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 12)
  - Annual Report, 1996-1997 (Box 2 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 13)
  - Annual Report, 1997-1998 (Box 2 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 14)
  - Annual Report, 1998-1999 (Box 2 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 15)
- Bylaws, Charters, and Faculty Handbooks, 1948-1992; 6; 0.33 cubic ft.
  - Faculty Handbook, 1948; 1952; 1962-1963; 1966 (Box 1 (6-Bylaws, Charters, and Faculty Handbooks), Folder 1)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1966-1967; 1971-1972 (Box 1 (6-Bylaws, Charters, and Faculty Handbooks), Folder 2)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1972-1974 (Box 1 (6-Bylaws, Charters, and Faculty Handbooks), Folder 3)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1975-1978 (Box 1 (6-Bylaws, Charters, and Faculty Handbooks), Folder 4)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1979-1982 (Box 1 (6-Bylaws, Charters, and Faculty Handbooks), Folder 5)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1984-1985; 1986-1987 (Box 1 (6-Bylaws, Charters, and Faculty Handbooks), Folder 6)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1989-1990; 1990-1992; 1992 (Box 1 (6-Bylaws, Charters, and Faculty Handbooks), Folder 7)
- Membership Lists, 1966-1998; 7; 0.33 cubic ft.
  Lists of members of the University Senate, including the membership of the specific councils and committees and student memberships.
  - Membership Lists of the Faculty Senate, 1966-1967; 1969-1970 (Box 1 (7-Membership Lists), Folder 1)
  - Membership Lists, 1970-1971; 1974/1975 (Box 1 (7-Membership Lists), Folder 2)
  - Membership Lists, 1975-1976; 1980-1981 (Box 1 (7-Membership Lists), Folder 3)
  - Membership Lists, 1981-1982; 1986-1987 (Box 1 (7-Membership Lists), Folder 4)
  - Membership Lists, 1987-1988; 1990-1991 (Box 1 (7-Membership Lists), Folder 5)
  - Membership Lists, 1991-1992; 1993-1994 (Box 1 (7-Membership Lists), Folder 6)
  - Membership Lists, 1994-1995; 1996-1997 (Box 1 (7-Membership Lists), Folder 7)
  - Membership Lists, 1997-1998 (Box 1 (7-Membership Lists), Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1966-1999; 8; 1 cubic ft.
  This series consists of the correspondence of the Chair of the University Senate, including Ronald A. Bosco (1983-84, 1989-90), William F. Hammond (1987-88, 1988-89), William Lanford (1990-91), Audrey Champagne (1993-94), Carlos Santiago (1996-97), and Sue Faerman (1997-98). It includes correspondence with the President of the University, the Chairs of the Councils of the University Senate, the University Faculty Senate, and the State of New York.
  - Correspondence, 1966 May - 1968 December (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - General, 1966-1968 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1969 January - 1969 October (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - General, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1969 November-1971 December (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Secretary of the Senate, 1969-1980 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Chair's Correspondence, 1969-1981 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - General, 1971 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Correspondence Re: Coffee Hours, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Archives - General Correspondence, 1971-1980 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1972 January-1986 February (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Correspondence - General, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - General, 1974 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Correspondence - General, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Correspondence - General, 1977 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Correspondence - General, 1978 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Correspondence - General, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Correspondence - General, 1979-1981 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Chair's Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Chair's Correspondence, 1984-1988 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 1988-1994 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Chair's Correspondence, 1989 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Correspondence with the University Faculty Senate, 1989-1993 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 23)
  - Chair's Correspondence, 1990 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 24)
  - Chair's Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Chair's Correspondence, 1993-1996 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Chair's Correspondence, 1997-1999 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 27)
  - Correspondence - General, Undated (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 28)
- Elections, 2004-2017; 9
  Arranged chronologically
  Election ballots and solicitations for service.
- Commencement, 2004-2013; 10
  Records of attendees and regalia orders.
- Plenaries, 2008-2014; 11
- Policies, Methology, and Instructions, 2012-2013; 12
- Subject Files, 1965-1999; 13; 1.67 cubic ft.
  Miscellaneous subject files maintained by the University Senate primarily relating to committees and task forces such as those on the environment, firearms, government, students ratings of faculty, as well as general correspondence files.
  - University Auxiliary Service, 1965-1976 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Clippings from Campus Courier, 1966-1969 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Parking, 1966-1974 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Physical Education, 1967-1972 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Salary Requests, 1967-1973 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Ph. D. Programs, 1967-1982 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Master's Programs, 1967-1983 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Certificate Programs, 1968-1979 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - B.A and B.S Programs, 1968-1981 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Faculty-Student Consultation, 1969-1971 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - The General College and Experimental College, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - S/U Grading, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Doctor of Arts Program, 1969-1972 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Academic Policy General Files, 1969-1977 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Clippings from Albany Student Press, 1969 September-1977 December (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - The CURE Proposal, 1970 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Clippings from the Tower Tribune, 1970-1973 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Affirmative Action - General Files, 1970-1976 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Graduate Academic Policy, 1970-1981 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Room Reservations, 1970-1989 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Middle States Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools - Accreditation, 1971 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Student Dwelling Incorporated, 1971 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - S/U Grading, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Emeritus Status, 1971-1973 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Communication Study, 1972 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Master Plan of the State University of New York - 1972. "Reaffirmation and Reform: Building a Comprehensive University for the 70's" (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Master Plan of the State University of New York, Summary Version - "Reaffirmation and Reform", 1972 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Pre-Registration (Lufti Proposal), 1972 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Firearms Policy (Folder 1), 1972-1973 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Withdrawal Policies, 1972-1978 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Faculty Senate Bulletin, 1973 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Prospectus for the University Center at Albany, 1973 March (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Prospectus for the University Center at Albany - Revised, 1973 June (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Fierarms Policy (Folder 2), 1973-1974 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - "Master Plan" or "Prospectus 1973-81" planning, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Clippings from Tower Tribune, 1973 October- 1977 December (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - S/U Grading, 1973-1984 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - United University Professions (UUP), 1974-1978 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Faculty Exchange Scholars Program, 1974-1981 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - American Association of University Professors (AAUP), 1975 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Prospectus for the University Center at Albany, 1975 July (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Five Quad Volunteer Ambulance Service, 1976 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - The Regents Tentative Statewide Plan for the Development of Postsecondary Education, 1976 November (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Regents Tentative Statewide Plan for the Development of Postsecondary Education, Undated (Box 2 (13-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Regents Tentative Statewide Plan for the Development of Postsecondary Education, Comments, Undated (Box 2 (13-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Regents Tentative Statewide Plan for the Development of Postsecondary Education, Second Draft, Undated (Box 2 (13-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Affirmative Action - General Files, Undated (Box 2 (13-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - University Auxiliary Service, Undated (Box 2 (13-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Academic Policy General Files, Undated (Box 2 (13-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Programs and Priorities; Abstracts of Three-Year Plans- State University of New York at Albany, Undated (Box 2 (13-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Programs and Priorities of the State University of New York at Albany, Undated (Box 2 (13-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - University "FACT" Book, Undated (Box 2 (13-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Truth-in-Testing Bill, Undated (Box 2 (13-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Budget Panel, Undated (Box 2 (13-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Academic Policy General Files, 1979-1981 (Box 3 (13-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Middle States Association of Colleges and Schools Evaluation, 1980 (Box 3 (13-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - R.O.T.C, 1980-1982 (Box 3 (13-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Student Instructional Rating Form (SIRF), 1980-1984 (Box 3 (13-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - The Undergraduate Bulletin, 1983-1984 (Box 3 (13-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Office Equipment, 1985-1987 (Box 3 (13-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Budget Materials, 1986 (Box 3 (13-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Affirmative Action Plan, 1989 (Box 3 (13-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - "Toward a Prosperous Future" - Report of the Policy Steering Committee of the Governor's Conference on Science and Engineering Education, Research and Development, 1990 (Box 3 (13-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Faculty Senate Bulletin, 1990-1995 (Box 3 (13-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - University operations Committee - Publication "Award for Excellence in Equal Opportunity/Affirmative Action", 1991 April (Box 3 (13-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - University operations Committee - Publication "A Longitudinal Profile of the Faculty by Gender and Ethnicity", 1993 April (Box 3 (13-Subject Files), Folder 12)